A Guide to the John D. Rockefeller, Sr. papers, Financial Material, Vouchers, Subseries FV FA262
Rockefeller Archive Center
John D. Rockefeller, Sr. papers, Financial Material, Vouchers, Subseries FV
1893-1916
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller, John D., Jr. (John Davison) (1874-1960)
FA262
184.73 Cubic Feet 484 letter document boxes, 2 half-letter, 1 wide letter document box
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Scope and Contents
Subseries FV primarily contains financial vouchers documenting the activities of John D. Rockefeller and John D. Rockefeller Jr. in the late 19th and early 20th century.
Arrangement
Alphabetical.
- Financial Material, 1893-1916; F; 184.73 Cubic Feet
  - Vouchers - A, FV 1
    - A1 - A285, 1894 March 1-May 3 (Box 1)
    - A286 - A510, 1894 May 3-June 14 (Box 2)
    - A486 - A685, 1894 June 14-August 13 (Box 3)
    - A686 - A875, 1894 August 16-October 10 (Box 4)
    - A876 - A1085, 1894 October 10-November 22 (Box 5)
    - A1086 - A1315, 1894 November 23-1895 January 5 (Box 6)
    - A1316 - A1575, 1895 January 5-February 28 (Box 7)
    - A1576 - A1810, 1895 February 28-April 28 (Box 8)
    - A1811 - A2040, 1895 April 28-June 26 (Box 9)
    - A2041 - A2260, 1895 June 26-August 27 (Box 10)
    - A2261 - A2475, 1895 August 26-November 2 (Box 11)
    - A2475 - A2680, 1895 November 2-December 12 (Box 12)
    - A2681 - A2930, 1895 December 12-1896 January 20 (Box 13)
    - A2930 - A3150, 1896 January 20-March 9 (Box 14)
    - A3151 - A3360, 1896 March 9-April 13 (Box 15)
    - A3361 - A3570, 1896 April 13-May 28 (Box 16)
    - A3571 - A3790, 1896 May 28-July 15 (Box 17)
    - A3791 - A4020, 1896 July 15-September 11 (Box 18)
    - A4021 - A4275, 1896 September 11-October 28 (Box 19)
    - A4276 - A4550, 1896 October 28-December 16 (Box 20)
    - A4551 - A4850, 1896 December 16-1897 February 4 (Box 21)
    - A4851 - A5090, 1897 February 4-March 27 (Box 22)
    - A5091 - A5375, 1897 March 27-May 22 (Box 23)
    - A5376 - A5620, 1897 May 22-July 7 (Box 24)
    - A5621 - A5870, 1897 July 7-August 17 (Box 25)
    - A5871 - A6110, 1897 August 17-October 12 (Box 26)
    - A6111 - A6355, 1897 October 12-November 24 (Box 27)
    - A6356 - A6625, 1897 November 24-1898 January 20 (Box 28)
    - A6626 - A6855, 1898 January 7-February 18 (Box 29)
    - A6856 - A7100, 1898 February 18-April 11 (Box 30)
    - A7101 - A7380, 1898 April 11-May 29 (Box 31)
    - A7381 - A7620, 1898 May 29-July 11 (Box 32)
    - A7621 - A7850, 1898 July 11-August 26 (Box 33)
    - A7851 - A8075, 1898 August 26-October 15 (Box 34)
    - A8076 - A8285, 1898 October 15-November 23 (Box 35)
    - A8326 - A8930, 1898 November 23-1899 March 15 (Box 36)
    - A8931 - A9185, 1899 March 15-May 5 (Box 37)
    - A9186 - A9425, 1899 May 5-June 15 (Box 38)
    - A9426 - A9660, 1899 June 15-July 28 (Box 39)
    - A9661 - A9900, 1899 July 28-September 21 (Box 40)
    - A9901 - A10150, 1899 September 21-November 11 (Box 41)
    - A10151 - A10430, 1899 November 11-December 20 (Box 42)
    - A10431 - A10685, 1899 December 20-1900 January 17 (Box 43)
    - A10686 - A10904, 1900 January 17-March 10 (Box 44)
    - A10941 - A11190, 1900 March 10-April 21 (Box 45)
    - A11191 - A11410, 1900 April 21-June 6 (Box 46)
    - A11411 - A11640, 1900 June 6-July 19 (Box 47)
    - A11641 - A11840, 1900 July 19-September 7 (Box 48)
    - A11841 - A12035, 1900 September 7-October 15 (Box 49)
    - A12036 - A12230, 1900 October 15-November 22 (Box 50)
    - A12230 - A12470, 1900 November 22-December 28 (Box 51)
    - A12471 - A12675, 1900 December 28-1901 January 30 (Box 52)
    - A12676 - A12870, 1901 January 30-February 27 (Box 53)
    - A12871 - A13050, 1901 February 27-April 5 (Box 54)
    - A13051 - A13250, 1901 April 5-May 7 (Box 55)
    - A13251 - A13505, 1901 May 7-June 13 (Box 56)
    - A13506 - A13700, 1901 June 14-July 12 (Box 57)
    - A13701 - A13930, 1901 July 12-August 19 (Box 58)
    - A13931 - A14135, 1901 August 19-September 30 (Box 59)
    - A14136 - A14345, 1901 September 30-November 7 (Box 60)
    - A14345 - A14555, 1901 November 7-December 6 (Box 61)
    - A14556 - A14835, 1901 December 6-January 6 (Box 62)
    - A14836 - A15080, 1902 January 6-February 10 (Box 63)
    - A15081 - A15335, 1902 February 10-March 20 (Box 64)
    - A15336 - A15591, 1902 March 20-April 26 (Box 65)
    - A15591 - A15800, 1902 April 26-May 24 (Box 66)
    - A15801 - A16025, 1902 May 24-June 24 (Box 67)
    - A16026 - A16260, 1902 June 24-July 25 (Box 68)
    - A16261 - A16475, 1902 July 25-September 5 (Box 69)
    - A16476 - A16710, 1902 September 5-October 7 (Box 70)
    - A16711 - A16950, 1902 October 7-November 5 (Box 71)
    - A16951 - A17200, 1902 November 5-December 5 (Box 72)
    - A17201 - A17500, 1902 December 5-31 (Box 73)
    - A17501 - A17735, 1902 December 31-1903 January 27 (Box 74)
    - A17736 - A18045, 1903 January 27-March 6 (Box 75)
    - A18046 - A18280, 1903 March 6-April 21 (Box 76)
    - A18286 - A18525, 1903 April 21-May 15 (Box 77)
    - A18526 - A18760, 1903 May 15-June 9 (Box 78)
    - A18761 - A19000, 1903 June 9-July 7 (Box 79)
    - A19001 - A19250, 1903 July 7-August 6 (Box 80)
    - A19251 - A19500, 1903 August 6-September 14 (Box 81)
    - A19501 - A19750, 1903 September 14-October 16 (Box 82)
    - A19751 - A20010, 1903 October 16-November 23 (Box 83)
    - A20011 - A20250, 1903 November 23-December 17 (Box 84)
    - A20251 - A20540, 1903 December 17-1904 January 13 (Box 85)
    - A20541 - A20800, 1904 January 13-February 18 (Box 86)
    - A20801 - A21015, 1904 February 18-March 18 (Box 87)
    - A21016 - A21200, 1904 March 18-April 18 (Box 88)
    - A21201 - A21425, 1904 April 8-May 5 (Box 89)
    - A21426 - A21650, 1904 May 5-June 3 (Box 90)
    - A21651 - A21865, 1904 June 3-20 (Box 91)
    - A21866 - A22100, 1904 June 20-July 18 (Box 92)
    - A22101 - A22330, 1904 July 18-August 11 (Box 93)
    - A22331 - A22570, 1904 August 11-September 15 (Box 94)
    - A22571 - A22790, 1904 September 15-October 13 (Box 95)
    - A22791 - A23100, 1904 October 15-November 23 (Box 96)
    - A23101 - A23449, 1904 November 25-December 28 (Box 97)
    - A23450 - A23789, 1904 December 28-1905 February 11 (Box 98)
    - A23790 - A24089, 1905 February 4-March 15 (Box 99)
    - A24090 - A24390, 1905 March 15-April 15 (Box 100)
    - A24391 - A24679, 1905 April 15-May 14 (Box 101)
    - A24680 - A24970, 1905 May 12-June 10 (Box 102)
    - A24971 - A25250, 1905 June 9-July 13 (Box 103)
    - A25251 - A25540, 1905 July 14-August 8 (Box 104)
    - A25541 - A25830, 1905 August 8-September 13 (Box 105)
    - A25831 - A26119, 1905 September 13-October 19 (Box 106)
    - A26120 - A26400, 1905 October 19-November 18 (Box 107)
    - A26401 - A26679, 1905 November 20-December 15 (Box 108)
    - A26680 - A27000, 1905 December 14-1906 January 10 (Box 109)
    - A27001 - A27240, 1906 January 11-31 (Box 110)
    - A27241 - A27554, 1906 January 31-March 6 (Box 111)
    - A27555 - A27889, 1906 March 6-April 6 (Box 112)
    - A27890 - A28240, 1906 April 6-May 12 (Box 113)
    - A28241 - A28570, 1906 May 12-June 13 (Box 114)
    - A28571 - A28850, 1906 June 14-July 10 (Box 115)
    - A28851 - A29169, 1906 July 5-August 17 (Box 116)
    - A29170 - A29439, 1906 August 17-September 19 (Box 117)
    - A29440 - A29750, 1906 September 19-October 12 (Box 118)
    - A29751 - A30015, 1906 October 18-November 17 (Box 119)
    - A30016 - A30314, 1906 November 18-December 14 (Box 120)
    - A30315 - A30692, 1906 December 13-1907 January 13 (Box 121)
    - A30693 - A30979, 1907 January 13-February 13 (Box 122)
    - A30980 - A31328, 1907 February 13-March 15 (Box 123)
    - A31329 - A31650, 1907 March 15-April 13 (Box 124)
    - A31651 - A31950, 1907 April 15-May 14 (Box 125)
    - A31951 - A32264, 1907 May 15-June 12 (Box 126)
    - A32265 - A32631, 1907 June 12-July 12 (Box 127)
    - A32632 - A32952, 1907 July 11-August 13 (Box 128)
    - A32953 - A33325, 1907 August 12-September 23 (Box 129)
    - A33326 - A33630, 1907 September 23-October 18 (Box 130)
    - A33631 - A33930, 1907 October 18-November 25 (Box 131)
    - A33931 - A34130, 1907 November 25-December 19 (Box 132)
    - A34171 - A34529, 1907 December 19-1908 January 15 (Box 133)
    - A34532 - A34805, 1908 January 15-February 14 (Box 134)
    - A34806 - A35080, 1908 February 14-March 17 (Box 135)
    - A35081 - A35370, 1908 March 16-April 20 (Box 136)
    - A35371 - A35600, 1908 April 20-May 14 (Box 137)
    - A35601 - A35860, 1908 May 14-June 11 (Box 138)
    - A35861 - A36139, 1908 June 12-July 1 (Box 139)
    - A36140 - A36400, 1908 July 1-25 (Box 140)
    - A36401 - A36660, 1908 July 22-August 19 (Box 141)
    - A36661 - A36920, 1908 August 19-September 12 (Box 142)
    - A36921 - A37200, 1908 September 12-October 7 (Box 143)
    - A37202 - A37480, 1908 October 7-28 (Box 144)
    - A37481 - A37750, 1908 November 2-25 (Box 145)
    - A37751 - A38040, 1908 November 25-December 23 (Box 146)
    - A38041 - A38400, 1908 December 23-1909 January 20 (Box 147)
    - A38401 - A38700, 1909 January 20-February 15 (Box 148)
    - A38701 - A38989, 1909 February 15-March 11 (Box 149)
    - A38990 - A39250, 1909 March 11-April 17 (Box 150)
    - A39251 - A39530, 1909 April 7-May 3 (Box 151)
    - A39531 - A39820, 1909 May 3-June 4 (Box 152)
    - A39821 - A40080, 1909 June 4-30 (Box 153)
    - A40081 - A40349, 1909 June 30-July 19 (Box 154)
    - A40351 - A40680, 1909 July 17-August 18 (Box 155)
    - A40681 - A40965, 1909 August 18-September 16 (Box 156)
    - A40966 - A41280, 1909 September 16-October 19 (Box 157)
    - A41281 - A41598, 1909 October 19-November 18 (Box 158)
    - A41600 - A41900, 1909 November 16-December 13 (Box 159)
    - A41901 - A42220, 1909 December 11-1910 January 8 (Box 160)
    - A42221 - A42440, 1910 January 10-15 (Box 161)
    - A42441 - A42680, 1910 January 27-February 18 (Box 162)
    - A42681 - A42935, 1910 February 18-March 16 (Box 163)
    - A42936 - A43160, 1910 March 16-April 8 (Box 164)
    - A43161 - A43400, 1910 April 8-27 (Box 165)
    - A43401 - A43640, 1910 April 27-May 17 (Box 166)
    - A43641 - A43880, 1910 May 17-June 10 (Box 167)
    - A43881 - A44060, 1910 June 10-29 (Box 168)
    - A44061 - A44300, 1910 June 29 - July 26 (Box 169)
    - A44301 - A44519, 1910 July 26-August 10 (Box 170)
    - A44520 - A44744, 1910 August 10-September 7 (Box 171)
    - A44745 - A44950, 1910 September 7-28 (Box 172)
    - A44951 - A45180, 1910 October 1-21 (Box 173)
    - A45181 - A45420, 1910 October 21-November 10 (Box 174)
    - A45421 - A45620, 1910 November 10-28 (Box 175)
    - A45621 - A45810, 1910 November 28-December 16 (Box 176)
    - A45811 - A46130, 1910 December 16-1911 January 10 (Box 177)
    - A46131 - A46360, 1911 January 11-30 (Box 178)
    - A46361 - A46610, 1911 January 30-February 24 (Box 179)
    - A46611 - A46840, 1911 February 24-March 15 (Box 180)
    - A46841 - A47090, 1911 March 15-April 5 (Box 181)
    - A47091 - A47330, 1911 April 5-May 1 (Box 182)
    - A47331 - A47540, 1911 May 1-16 (Box 183)
    - A47541 - A47770, 1911 May 16-June 6 (Box 184)
    - A47771 - A48020, 1911 June 7-28 (Box 185)
    - A48021 - A48225, 1911 June 28-July 11 (Box 186)
    - A48226 - A48420, 1911 July 11-31 (Box 187)
    - A48420 - A48640, 1911 July 31-August 25 (Box 188)
    - A48641 - A48890, 1911 August 25-September 19 (Box 189)
    - A48891 - A49115, 1911 September 19-October 10 (Box 190)
    - A49116 - A49295, 1911 October 10-30 (Box 191)
    - A49296 - A49510, 1911 October 30-November 10 (Box 192)
    - A49511 - A49710, 1911 November 10-December 1 (Box 193)
    - A49711 - A49900, 1911 December 1-13 (Box 194)
    - A49901 - A50155, 1911 December 13-29 (Box 195)
    - A50156 - A50370, 1911 December 29-1912 January 16 (Box 196)
    - A50371 - A50600, 1912 January 16-February 2 (Box 197)
    - A50601 - A50790, 1912 February 2-14 (Box 198)
    - A50791 - A51041, 1912 February 14-March 4 (Box 199)
    - A51042 - A51240, 1912 March 4-18 (Box 200)
    - A51241 - A51485, 1912 March 18-April 3 (Box 201)
    - A51486 - A51680, 1912 April 3-17 (Box 202)
    - A51681 - A51905, 1912 April 17-May 7 (Box 203)
    - A51906 - A52100, 1912 May 7-22 (Box 204)
    - A52101 - A52310, 1912 May 22-June 10 (Box 205)
    - A52311 - A52530, 1912 June 10-29 (Box 206)
    - A52531 - A52750, 1912 July 1-12 (Box 207)
    - A52751 - A52970, 1912 July 12-30 (Box 208)
    - A52971 - A53180, 1912 July 30-August 15 (Box 209)
    - A53181 - A53370, 1912 August 15-September 5 (Box 210)
    - A53371 - A53580, 1912 September 5-25 (Box 211)
    - A53581 - A53810, 1912 September 25-October 9 (Box 212)
    - A53811 - A54020, 1912 October 9-28 (Box 213)
    - A54021 - A54220, 1912 October 29-November 12 (Box 214)
    - A54221 - A54400, 1912 November 12-29 (Box 215)
    - A54401 - A54631, 1912 November 29-December 16 (Box 216)
    - A54632 - A54845, 1912 December 16-30 (Box 217)
    - A54846 - A54998, 1912 December 30-1913 January 8 (Box 218)
    - A54999 - A55166, 1913 January 8-27 (Box 219)
    - A55167 - A55410, 1913 January 27-February 1 (Box 220)
    - A55411 - A55565, 1913 February 10-24 (Box 221)
    - A55566 - A55780, 1913 February 24-March 8 (Box 222)
    - A55781 - A55930, 1913 March 8-24 (Box 223)
    - A55931 - A56150, 1913 March 24-April 8 (Box 224)
    - A56151 - A56330, 1913 April 8-16 (Box 225)
    - A56331 - A56550, 1913 April 17-30 (Box 226)
    - A56551 - A56730, 1913 April 30-May 14 (Box 227)
    - A56731 - A56865, 1913 May 14-23 (Box 228)
    - A56866 - A57080, 1913 May 23-June 9 (Box 229)
    - A57081 - A57280, 1913 June 9-25 (Box 230)
    - A57281 - A57490, 1913 June 25-July 7 (Box 231)
    - A57491 - A57700, 1913 July 7-16 (Box 232)
    - A57701 - A57960, 1913 July 22-August 9 (Box 233)
    - A57961 - A58139, 1913 August 9-20 (Box 234)
    - A58141 - A58385, 1913 August 20-September 8 (Box 235)
    - A58386 - A58580, 1913 September 8-19 (Box 236)
    - A58581 - A58854, 1913 September 23-October 8 (Box 237)
    - A58856 - A59085, 1913 October 8-31 (Box 238)
    - A59086 - A59290, 1913 October 27-November 8 (Box 239)
    - A59292 - A59464, 1913 November 7-20 (Box 240)
    - A59467 - A59670, 1913 November 17-December 3 (Box 241)
    - A59670 - A59865, 1913 December 3-22 (Box 242)
    - A59866 - A60220, 1913 December 22-1914 January 6 (Box 243)
    - A60221 - A60440, 1914 January 7-17 (Box 244)
    - A60441 - A60625, 1914 January 19-30 (Box 245)
    - A60626 - A60890, 1914 February 2-13 (Box 246)
    - A60891 - A61100, 1914 February 13-28 (Box 247)
    - A61101 - A61260, 1914 March 4-12 (Box 248)
    - A61261 - A61470, 1914 March 12-30 (Box 249)
    - A61471 - A61700, 1914 March 30-April 9 (Box 250)
    - A61701 - A61880, 1914 April 11-25 (Box 251)
    - A61881 - A62119, 1914 April 25-May 6 (Box 252)
    - A62122 - A62340, 1914 May 9-27 (Box 253)
    - A62360 - A62585, 1914 May 29-June 12 (Box 254)
    - A62586 - A62790, 1914 June 12-26 (Box 255)
    - A62791 - A63080, 1914 June 26-July 14 (Box 256)
    - A63081 - A63230, 1914 July 14-22 (Box 257)
    - A63231 - A63441, 1914 August 5-25 (Box 258)
    - A63471 - A63655, 1914 August 5-25 (Box 259)
    - A63656 - A63910, 1914 August 25-September 9 (Box 260)
    - A63911 - A64090, 1914 September 9-28 (Box 261)
    - A64091 - A64330, 1914 September 28-October 8 (Box 262)
    - A64331 - A64520, 1914 October 8-24 (Box 263)
    - A64521 - A64712, 1914 October 22-November 9 (Box 264)
    - A64713 - A64920, 1914 November 9-21 (Box 265)
    - A64921 - A65145, 1914 November 20-December 7 (Box 266)
    - A65146 - A65400, 1914 December 7-21 (Box 267)
    - A65408 - A65510, 1914 December 15-31 (Box 268)
  - Vouchers - B, FV 2
    - 11 - 190, 1901 May 4-July 24 (Box 1)
    - 191 - 374, 1901 July 31-October 4 (Box 2)
    - 375 - 566, 1901 September 23-December 7 (Box 3)
    - 567 - 764, 1901 December 7-1902 March 13 (Box 4)
    - 765 - 928, 1902 March 13-July 15 (Box 5)
    - 929 - 1061, 1902 July 15-October 2 (Box 6)
    - 1062 - 1197, 1902 October 1-November 17 (Box 7)
    - 1198 - 1332, 1902 November 19-1903 January 7 (Box 8)
    - 1333 - 1484, 1903 January 7-March 11 (Box 9)
    - 1485 - 1632, 1903 March 11-June 18 (Box 10)
    - 1633 - 2086, 1903 June 19-1908 February 8 (Box 11)
    - 2087 - 2286, 1908 February 13-October 7 (Box 12)
    - 2287 - 2464, 1908 October 7-1909 March 28 (Box 13)
    - 2465 - 2637, 1909 March 30-November 13 (Box 14)
    - 2638 - 2781, 1909 November 16-1910 December 30 (Box 15)
    - 2782 - 2856, 1911 January 6-1912 March 18 (Box 16)
  - Vouchers - PH, FV 3
    - 1 - 196 (Box 1)
    - 196 - 370 (Box 2)
    - 371 - 577 (Box 3)
    - 578 - 814 (Box 4)
    - 815 - 1038 (Box 5)
    - 1039 - 1168 (Box 6)
    - 1169 - 1383 (Box 7)
    - 1384 - 1582 (Box 8)
    - 1583 - 1776 (Box 9)
    - 1777 - 1950 (Box 10)
    - 1951 - 2169 (Box 11)
    - 2170 - 2346 (Box 12)
    - 2347 - 2495 (Box 13)
    - 2496 - 2665 (Box 14)
    - 2666 - 2791 (Box 15)
    - 2792 - 2956 (Box 16)
    - 2957 - 3100 (Box 17)
  - Vouchers - O, FV 4
    - O1510 - O1718, 1916 April 26-July 31 (Box 1)
  - Vouchers - JR - H, FV 5
    - H1862 - H2175, 1907 May 4-September 30 (Box 1)
    - H2176 - H2529, 1907 October 1-1908 February 21 (Box 2)
    - H2530 - H2860, 1908 February 24-October 7 (Box 3)
    - H2861 - H3149, 1908 June 12-October 7 (Box 4)
    - H3150 - H3457, 1908 October 7-1909 January 18 (Box 5)
    - H3458 - H3759, 1909 January 25-April 1 (Box 6)
    - H3760 - H4069, 1909 April 1-August 1 (Box 7)
    - H4070 - H4369, 1909 August 1-December 1 (Box 8)
    - H4373 - H4659, 1909 December 10-1910 February 28 (Box 9)
    - H4660 - H4905, 1910 February 28-June 1 (Box 10)
    - H4906 - H5176, 1910 June 1-August 22 (Box 11)
    - H577 - H5428, 1910 August 22-October 27 (Box 12)
    - H5429 - H5719, 1910 October 27-1911 January 13 (Box 13)
    - H5720 - H5980, 1911 January 13-March 16 (Box 14)
    - H5981 - H6264, 1911 March 16-June 13 (Box 15)
    - H6264 - H6501, 1911 June 13-August 14 (Box 16)
    - H6502 - H6723, 1911 August 14-October 28 (Box 17)
    - H6724 - H6950, 1911 October 30-1912 January 3 (Box 18)
    - H6951 - H7160, 1912 January 3-March 1 (Box 19)
    - H7161 - H7370, 1912 March 1-May 3 (Box 20)
    - H7371 - H7573, 1912 May 3-July 3 (Box 21)
    - H7574 - H7762, 1912 July 3-August 26 (Box 22)
    - H7763 - H7946, 1912 August 26-October 8 (Box 23)
    - H7947 - H8135, 1912 October 8-November 26 (Box 24)
    - H8136 - H8324, 1912 November 26-1913 January 6 (Box 25)
    - H8325 - H8504, 1913 January 6-February 10 (Box 26)
    - H8505 - H8696, 1913 February 10-April 9 (Box 27)
    - H8697 - H8895, 1913 April 9-May 28 (Box 28)
    - H8896 - H9086, 1913 May 29-July 14 (Box 29)
    - H9087 - H9301, 1913 July 14-September 9 (Box 30)
    - H9302 - H9504, 1913 September 9-October 22 (Box 31)
    - H9505 - H9700, 1913 October 23-December 3 (Box 32)
    - H9701 - H9890, 1913 December 3-1914 January 6 (Box 33)
    - H9891 - H10070, 1914 January 6-February 10 (Box 34)
    - H10071 - H10250, 1914 February 11-March 23 (Box 35)
    - H10251 - H10410, 1914 March 23-April 24 (Box 36)
    - H10411 - H10600, 1914 April 27-June 8 (Box 37)
    - H10601 - H10780, 1914 June 8-July 16 (Box 38)
    - H10781 - H10950, 1914 July 16-August 31 (Box 39)
    - H10951 - H11120, 1914 September 1-October 9 (Box 40)
    - H11121 - H11285, 1914 October 9-November 25 (Box 41)
    - H11286 - H11473, 1914 November 25-December 23 (Box 42)
    - H11473 - H11650, 1914 December 24-1915 February 8 (Box 43)
    - H11651 - H11831, 1915 February 8-March 12 (Box 44)
    - H11831 - H12031, 1915 March 12-May 1 (Box 45)
    - H12031 - H12240, 1915 May 4-June 21 (Box 46)
    - H12241 - H12430, 1915 June 21-July 16 (Box 47)
    - H12431 - H12460, H12581 - H12600, 1915 July 26-August 27 (Box 48)
    - H12601 - H12780, 1914 August 30-October 1 (Box 49)
    - H12781 - H12970, 1915 October 1-November 1 (Box 50)
    - H12971 - H13160, 1915 November 1-December 10 (Box 51)
    - H13161 - H13360, 1915 December 10-1916 January 8 (Box 52)
    - H13361 - H13550, 1916 January 8-February 1 (Box 53)
    - H13551 - H13730, 1916 February 2-March 4 (Box 54)
    - H13731 - H13910, 1916 March 4-April 8 (Box 55)
    - H13911 - H14100, 1916 April 8-May 6 (Box 56)
    - H14101 - H14310, 1916 May 6-June 7 (Box 57)
    - H14311 - H14500, 1916 June 7-July 1 (Box 58)
    - H14502 - H14650, 1916 June 28-July 18 (Box 59)
    - H14651 - H14722, 1916 July 18-31 (Box 60)
  - Vouchers - JR, FV 6
    - 1 - 354, 1907 January 10-1909 June 21 (Box 1)
    - 355 - 407, 694 - 743, 1909 June 22-1910 September 29 (Box 2)
    - 744 - 1026, 1910 September 29-1911 July 29 (Box 3)
    - 1027 - 1244, 1911 July 29-1912 April 1 (Box 4)
    - 1246 - 1420, 1912 April 4-October 22 (Box 5)
    - 1421 - 1607, 1912 October 23-1913 March 12 (Box 6)
    - 1608 - 1765, 1913 March 13-July 30 (Box 7)
    - 1766 - 1860, 1913 August 1-October 31 (Box 8)
    - 1861 - 2158, 1913 October 31-1914 June 18 (Box 9)
    - 2159 - 2421, 1914 June 18-1915 January 22 (Box 10)
    - 2422 - 2620, 1915 January 22-1916 January 29 (Box 11)
  - Vouchers - L, FV 7
    - L21401 - L21620, 1901 June 7-August 16 (Box 1)
    - L21620 - L21830, 1901 August 16-November 8 (Box 2)
    - L21831 - L22040, 1901 November 8-1902 January 2 (Box 3)
    - L22041 - L22270, 1902 January 2-March 31 (Box 4)
    - L22271 - L22530, 1902 March 31-June 24 (Box 5)
    - L22531 - L22810, 1902 June 24-September 17 (Box 6)
    - L22811 - L23120, 1902 September 16-1903 January 12 (Box 7)
    - L23121 - L23400, 1903 January 12-May 21 (Box 8)
    - L23401 - L23590, 1903 May 21-July 6 (Box 9)
    - L23591 - L23830, 1903 July 6-August 29 (Box 10)
    - L23831 - L24060, 1903 August 29-October 23 (Box 11)
    - L24061 - L24300, 1903 October 23-1904 January 7 (Box 12)
    - L24301 - L24560, 1904 January 7-April 28 (Box 13)
    - L24561 - L24770, 1904 April 28-July 15 (Box 14)
    - L24771 - L25040, 1904 July 15-November 14 (Box 15)
    - L25041 - L25250, 1904 November 14-1905 January 31 (Box 16)
    - L25251 - L25510, 1905 January 31-May 4 (Box 17)
    - L25511 - L25730, 1905 May 4-July 17 (Box 18)
    - L25731 - L25940, 1905 July 17-November 2 (Box 19)
    - L25941 - L26200, 1905 November 2-1906 January 30 (Box 20)
    - L26201 - L26440, 1906 January 30-April 11 (Box 21)
    - L26441 - L26690, 1906 April 12-June 4 (Box 22)
    - L26690 - L26980, 1906 June 6-September 28 (Box 23)
    - L26981 - L27310, 1906 September 28-1907 March 17 (Box 24)
    - L27311 - L27490, 1907 March 18-May 13 (Box 25)
    - L27491 - L27700, 1907 May 13-June 18 (Box 26)
    - L27701 - L27890, 1907 June 18-October 1 (Box 27)
    - L27891 - L28060, 1907 October 1-25 (Box 28)
    - L28061 - L28240, 1907 October 25-December 10 (Box 29)
    - L28241 - L28450, 1907 December 10-1908 January 10 (Box 30)
    - L28452 - L28630, 1908 January 10-February 5 (Box 31)
    - L28631 - L28825, 1908 February 6-April 9 (Box 32)
    - L28826 - L29000, 1908 April 9-May 14 (Box 33)
    - L29001 - L29180, 1908 May 14-June 10 (Box 34)
    - L29181 - L29380, 1908 June 10-July 23 (Box 35)
    - L29381 - L29560, 1908 July 23-August 13 (Box 36)
    - L29561 - L29740, 1908 August 13-25 (Box 37)
    - L29741 - L29920, 1908 August 25-September 17 (Box 38)
    - L29921 - L30094, 1908 September 17-October 7 (Box 39)
    - L30095 - L30280, 1908 October 7-November 25 (Box 40)
    - L30281 - L30477, 1908 November 25-December 31 (Box 41)
    - L30478 - L30680, 1909 January 4-March 11 (Box 42)
    - L30681 - L30870, 1909 March 11-April 20 (Box 43)
    - L30871 - L31090, 1909 April 20-June 7 (Box 44)
    - L31091 - L31540, 1909 June 7-August 14 (Box 45)
    - L31541 - L31748, 1909 August 16-September 24 (Box 46)
    - L31751 - L31939, 1909 September 27-November 9 (Box 47)
    - L31941 - L32150, 1909 November 9-December 17 (Box 48)
    - L32151 - L32360, 1909 December 17-1910 January 14 (Box 49)
    - L32421 - L32580, 1910 January 14-26 (Box 50)